Everyone!
Hold on!
Oh no!
It's sunk into the sand.
We should all be alright as long as
we don't move and don't make a sound.
It's much too late to try
hiding from me at this point.
I know where each of you landed.
There's no escaping now.
Four, no five steps.
I get it.
You're walking quietly to avoid detection.
But you can't hide from me.
It appears these steps
have thrown him for a lube.
Go ahead, you accursed water stand.
Just try to attack us.
Because the moment you reveal yourself,
I'll vaporize you with the
power of my magician's red.
Yeah.
You know.
I'm. I'm.
Oh.
I'm.
I'm not sure how much I can do it.
In the middle of the era of waiting,
You are going to run the time of war?
Stop.
It's now
The story of nook which you haven't had,
You're going to be part of the song,
Now the world to show you
what you're going to be?
You're going to continue
the song to be part of it.
I'm gonna take your way to the end.
It's on the last page of the last one.
The tale of an
end of the world.
The title of that.
That's the memory of the death.
Ola Ola Ola Ola.
The story
of the game.
He's here.
Hold on. What's this?
He only moved five steps forward.
How strange.
Why's he suddenly stopped moving?
No!
Magicians, run!
What?
Abdaal!
How can he be so...
so quick?
Abdaal!
I have to admit, that plan was
actually a stroke of brilliance.
I have to pay more attention to
their vibrations from now on.
Those weren't footsteps at all.
It would seem as though he
threw some kind of metal rings.
And judging by these burns,
I'd say Avdol did the deed.
But c 'est la vie.
Farewell.
Avdol.
What's this?
Someone started running.
Jotaro, what are you doing?
You know we can't just run around!
His stride says he's about
190, no, 195 centimeters tall.
There's a youthfulness in his
stride, so he's not Joseph.
It must be Jotaro then, but
where exactly is he going?
It dove in!
I think it's going after Jotaro!
This can't be happening!
I'm grateful he's not attacking
Avdol anymore, but... Jotaro!
He's catching up to you!
I hear Jotaro's Star Platinum is
the fiercest of the enemy's stands.
Master Dio will be beside himself with
joy if I take care of him here and now.
In the name of Master Dio,
I'll use every fiber of my being
to finally vanquish Jotaro.
If I heard correctly, Jotaro just
picked something up off the sand.
Let's see.
What was at that location?
Last I checked, it was...
Wait, I remember. The dog.
Jotaro grabbed the dog,
which means he knows.
I finally figured you out, mutt.
I know you jumped out of the car
before the stand attacked it.
You can smell it, can't you?
You know where it's gonna
be before it gets there.
Don't stop moving, Jotaro!
Now, Iggy, I think it's time
for you to earn your keep.
Where's the stand coming from?
Just show me already.
Show me or we die.
And how would you get your gum then?
Higgy!
You've got to be kidding me.
He can fly too?
Not so fast!
Go ahead and pan all you want.
You're not getting out of this one.
Star Platinums as fast as they come.
If you're thinking of dropping me, I'll
snap your neck before you can blink.
What?
It's like he jumped and
suddenly disappeared.
This is impossible.
They must have landed somewhere.
That's brilliant.
We can't move around.
So to bypass that handicap, Jotaro's
using Iggy to find the stand user.
If we can find whoever's
controlling the stand,
we might actually have a
chance of defeating him.
He's vanished.
I can't hear Jotaro's
footsteps. Where is he?
Where did he go?
Why can't I hear his footsteps?
Oh no, they're flying lower and lower.
This isn't gonna end well.
It looks like the fool
can't travel long distances.
The damn thing is gliding
like a paper airplane!
My legs are about to touch the ground.
Hey, Ma, quit tensing up like that.
You're starting to fart again.
For your sake, you better
not let out a big one.
No choice.
We need to get more air.
And at this point, there's
only one way to do it.
That kick got us a lot closer
to our destination, for sure.
But the sound of it definitely
gave away our strategy.
Now the user will know that
we're flying to avoid detection.
So that's why I wasn't
able to locate them.
The dog's stand has the ability to fly.
But now I know what they're up to.
They're headed directly for me.
I have to eliminate Jotaro
before he gets any closer.
His stand's on the move,
and it's going after Jotaro!
He figured it out when Jotaro kicked off!
There's nothing we can do about it.
The only thing we can
do now is trust Jotaro.
He's coming.
I know he was able to
bring down a helicopter,
but he shouldn't be able
to find our exact location?
since Iggy's stand barely makes a sound.
I just have to get to the stand user
before landing, and it'll be lights out.
There he is!
The stand user's about 400 meters away.
And from the looks of
things, our enemy is blind.
Damn it!
The sand's falling from the sky!
Of course!
The stand user must be trying to find us.
He's using the sand bouncing off the
wings like a submarine uses sonar.
Because of the falling
sand, I can hear you now.
And I've discovered your exact location.
Jotaro!
Time to die!
Star Platinum!
Star Platinum's speed won't
be of much use, I'm afraid.
If you can't tell where my attack is coming
from, then my stand has the advantage.
Here comes another!
Shit!
You damn mutt!
What a dog!
He's dragging Jotaro right into my trap!
It seems like he'll do
anything to save his own hide!
Even abandon his master!
Bastard, just you wait.
That's what you get for relying
on such a fickle creature, Jotaro.
Your end has come.
And now it's finally time to
put you out of your misery.
What's this?
It feels like he just
threw something at me.
I can't make out what it is at that speed.
I tossed Iggy at you.
Get a move on.
You'd better use your
stand to defend yourselves,
or else you two are gonna be
closer than you ever wanted to be.
Such insane velocity!
Damn it, it's going to hit me!
I can't believe it!
He actually threw the dog!
Ah, blast it!
I was so close to putting an end
to that wretch once and for all!
No, I was so busy worrying about that damn
dog, I completely lost Jotaro's location!
Where?
Where is he?
It's like he vanished, and
he's staying absolutely still.
That must have been his plan.
Where the hell are you?
You can't hide forever.
Show yourself, Jotaro!
I'm right here.
I see.
I didn't realize you'd slink so close.
If I hadn't had the foresight to
protect myself with this water shield,
you would have already
knocked me out from behind.
I suppose I should count myself lucky
it makes for such a good defense.
Given that we're now in
such close proximity,
I no longer need this cane to hear you.
However, I will require
its use when I return home.
I can't believe it.
It's hard to believe
but you actually managed
to knock off my hat
you can relax a little!
I was holding back
you're not going to die.
What the?
Why the hell would you
use your stand to explain?
Why did you do it?
Jotaro,
you thought you could manipulate
me and force me to tell
you information regarding
the other eight stand users,
didn't you?
I'm very well aware that Joseph Joestar's
Hermit Purple can view
into the minds of others.
You'll never get inside my head,
and I'll never tell you anything
that you could use against my master.
Dio, I don't understand
why you're so loyal to him.
Are you honestly telling
me that you'd die for him?
Jotaro, you're right.
You don't understand.
Fear of death holds no place in my heart.
Because of the power
of my stand I've always
been able to live a life
Unencumbered by such
inconsequential fears
like death I could always
win any fight I could have
and do whatever I wanted
Killing and stealing were
absolutely meaningless to me
You should talk to the Mott about
it I'm sure he knows how I feel
Dio was the first person
who was able to look
deep within my soul and
find something more.
He was the one who gave
me a desire to live.
That glorious force of nature.
He was so strong, so wise, so beautiful.
He was the one and only person in my life
to ever see a purpose for my existence.
I waited such a long time for
an opportunity to meet him.
I will gladly die for my master's sake.
But no matter what, I refuse to
do anything that would disappoint.
And after all, evil or not, a scoundrel
needs someone to put his faith in.
I'll tell you this before I go.
You should know that my name is N'Doul,
and my stand hails from Egypt,
the birthplace of the Tarot.
It's referred to as one of the Nine
Gods of Egypt, Geb of the Great Ennead.
We call it the God of the Earth.
Nine Egyptian gods?
What does that mean?
Sorry, but I'll only
tell you about my stand.
It's only fair since you're the
one who ended up stopping me.
But info on my compatriots
goes with me to my grave.
Dio brainwashes people.
Like a cult leader just
who is this guy exactly
and what's this crap about
the nine gods of egypt?
It's all a mystery but for now we
just have to keep moving forward.
Hey you don't have to be defensive it's
not like a manger with you or anything.
Makes sense to be pissed
i doubt you wanted
to be dragged out into
the desert and forced
into Some human crap
your position must suck
ass no one can blame you for being upset.
Iggy here you want some gum?
Could you calm down already i'm
trying to apologize take it.
Good grief that dog is
a pain in the ass you
can stay out here in the
desert for all i care.
Huh.
Well, what do you know?
You went back and fetched my hat for me.
Maybe you're not so bad after all.
Thanks.
You put gum in here?
You good for nothing little!
You're no ordinary mutt!
Hey!
Jotaro!
Are you alright?
Good grief.
Thank you.
Oh, sweet! Hey there!
Is that a comic book
you're reading, little man?
I've never seen one here.
So Egyptians read comics just like the
rest of us you want so many doughnuts?
Hey, mind if I see your comic book?
If you let me, I promise I'll
be super careful with it!
I'm a comic book artist who's
searching for inspiration.
Nothing gets me jazzed up more than
checking out rare books and comics.
Let me borrow it and you
can use my binoculars
What the hell peculiar the stories
about these two eerie looking brothers.
I don't see the creator's name
Wow, these are all such bizarre drawings.
But this is fantastic print quality,
not to mention it's in full color.
There once lived two brothers
who got along very well.
My name is Zenyatta.
My name is Mondatta.
Mondatta, the younger brother,
was very shy and wouldn't do anything
unless Zenyatta was with him.
He was always alone.
One day, while his big brother
Zenyatta was away, Monday,
Mondatta met a kind traveler
near the side of the road.
He gave Mondatta yummy snacks
and let him use his binoculars.
Mondatta had more fun than
he'd had in a long time.
Oh, it's 10.30.
But unfortunately, the very kind traveler
was impaled on a telephone
pole and died a horrific death.
Quite a weird comic you've got.
Is this comic especially
popular in this place?
If you ask me, it's really strange.
The other pages are all blank.
It's like they forgot to print the rest.
Must be a dud.
But somehow, I feel as though
I have a connection to it.
It's totally pulled me in.
This is gonna sound crazy,
but would it be possible for
me to buy this book from you?
It's not for sale.
Are you deaf or something?
My bro's book's not for sale.
Now get out of my sight.
This kid is your brother?
I won't tell you again!
Hey, what have I told you
about talking to strangers?
There's lots of bad people roaming
the world these days, you know?
Last call!
The bus for Aswan is
getting ready to depart!
That's us.
They're on their way to
the hospital in Aswan to
drop off their friend and
have his injuries treated.
Ah, you don't say.
If that's how it is, we'll just
have to wait for the next bus.
I don't know.
You and I are invincible together.
Who the hell is in our car?
It was me.
Couldn't you tell?
Jotaro, where's your school uniform?
You're acting really weird today.
The way you're clasping your hands.
Then that would mean no.
But the prediction can't be changed.
I believe in you, brother.